MIN WOO PARK PH.D. STUDENT

RESEARCH INTEREST My research focuses on Causal Decision Making and Causal Effect Identification. I study how to graphically model a wide range of real-world problems in a causal manner and make optimal decisions. In particular, my research explores methods for making robust decisions, even when modeling with incomplete information, and decision-making processes in sequential settings.

EDUCATION

Graduate School of Data Science, Seoul National University

Seoul

M.S and Ph.D integrated course in Data Science

2022 - present

- Advisor: Prof. Sanghack Lee
- Research area: Causal Decision Making, Causal Effect Identification
- GPA: 4.17/4.3

Department of Mathematics and Statistics, Sejong University

Seoul

B.S. in Applied Statistic and B.S. in Mathematics (Double Major)

2016 - 2022

- Advisor: Prof. Jieun Lee
- Research area: Operator Theory
- Overall GPA: 4.04/4.5 (Cum Laude)
- Major GPA: 4.46 & 4.38 / 4.5

Work Experience

Graduate School of Data Science, Seoul National University

Causality Lab

Jan 2023 - present

Department of Mathematics and Statistics, Sejong University

Functional Analysis Lab

Jul 2021 - Dec 2022

Korea Military Service

National Service Conscript

Aug 2016 - Nov 2018

PUBLICATIONS

- Complete Graphical Criterion for Sequential Covariate Adjustment in Causal Inference Yonghan Jung[†], Min Woo Park, and Sanghack Lee[†] Neural Information Processing Systems (NeurIPS), 2024.
- 2. Convergence of the iterated mean transforms of a 2×2 matrix Ji Eun Lee* † and Min Woo Park* preprint, 2024.
- 3. Computation of the iterated Aluthge, Duggal, and Mean transforms Min Woo Park*, and Ji Eun Lee*† *Filomat*, 2023.
- * for joint first authorship and † for corresponding author

Awards and Honors

5th place Award 2023 Mr. SNU body building competition	May 2023
4th place Award The 9th College of Natural Sciences Academic Confe	erence Nov 2021
First Place Academic Scholarship Sejong University	Fall 2021
Third Place Award The 8th College of Natural Sciences Academic Con	nference Nov 2020
First Place Academic Scholarship Sejong University	Fall 2020

Teaching Assistants	Causal Inference for Data Science Hyundai NGV Data Boot-Campus Causal Inference for Data Science Machine Learning and Deep Learning for Data Science II Basic Mathematics for Artificial Intelligence	Fall 2024 July 2024 - Sep 2024 Spring 2024 Fall 2023 Spring 2022
Invited Talks	SNU GSDS Pizza Seminar Complete Graphical Criterion for Sequential Covariate Adjustment in Causal Inference	Dec 2024
Reference	Sanghack Lee Seoul National University Assistant professor	sanghack@snu.ac.kr
	Ji Eun Lee Sejong University Associate Professor	jieunlee7@sejong.ac.kr

Last updated: Nov 22, 2024